[
	{
		"question": "When did India became a republic country?",
		"options": [
			"January 26, 1947",
			"August 15, 1947",
			"January 26, 1950",
			"August 15, 1950"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was the first nuclear bomb dropped?",
		"options": [
			"Hiroshima, Japan",
			"Moscow, Russia",
			"Tokyo, Japan",
			"Berlin, Germany"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first president of USA?",
		"options": [
			"George Bush",
			"George Washington",
			"John Kennedy",
			"Abraham Lincoln"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first indian prime minister?",
		"options": [
			"Mahatma Gandhi",
			"Rabindranath Tagore",
			"Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
			"Jawaharlal Nehru"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the former name of Mumbai?",
		"options": [
			"Calcutta",
			"Quilon",
			"Varanasi",
			"Bombay"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What was Adolf Hitler's nationality?",
		"options": [
			"German",
			"Russian",
			"American",
			"Austrian"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was tea invented?",
		"options": [
			"India",
			"China",
			"England",
			"Australia"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the author of the Indian national anthem?",
		"options": [
			"Aurobindo Ghosh",
			"Kamala Surayya",
			"Rabindranath Tagore",
			"Sarojini Naidu"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which king built the Taj Mahal?",
		"options": [
			"Shah Jahan",
			"Akbar",
			"Chandragupta Maurya",
			"Tipu Sultan"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who has invaded the most countries in history?",
		"options": [
			"Afghanistan",
			"Germany",
			"Britain",
			"Soviet Union"
		],
		"answer": 2
	}
]